<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./2048.sh</path>
		<name>2048</name>
		<image>./media/2048.png</image>
		<desc>A port of the popular puzzle game 2048 to libretro.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./AM2R.sh</path>
		<name>Another Metroid 2 Remake</name>
		<image>./media/AM2R.png</image>
		<desc>AM2R is a fan made remake of Metroid 2, with new gameplay, updated 16 bit style graphics, and an original soundtrack.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blues Brothers.sh</path>
		<name>Blues Brothers</name>
		<image>./media/Blues Brothers.png</image>
		<desc>The Blues Brothers are on the run from the law. Take control of either bulky Jake or nippy Elwood in this five-level platform game. You must cross a prison, a river and the big city to reach freedom</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blues Brothers Jukebox Adventure.sh</path>
		<name>Blues Brothers Jukebox Adventure</name>
		<image>./media/Blues Brothers Jukebox Adventure.png</image>
		<desc>The Blues Brothers: Jukebox Adventure is a video game based on the band The Blues Brothers, and a sequel to The Blues Brothers</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cannonball.sh</path>
		<name>Cannonball</name>
		<image>./media/Cannonball.png</image>
		<desc>A port of the Cannonball enhanced OutRun engine to libretro.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cave Story.sh</path>
		<name>Cave Story</name>
		<image>./media/Cave Story.png</image>
		<desc>An open-source reimplementation of the Cave Story / Doukutsu engine, ported to libretro.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cave Story-evo.sh</path>
		<name>Cave Story-evo</name>
		<image>./media/Cave Story-evo.png</image>
		<desc>An upgraded open-source reimplementation of the Cave Story / Doukutsu engine.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./C-Dogs.sh</path>
		<name>C-Dogs</name>
		<image>./media/C-Dogs.png</image>
		<desc>C-Dogs SDL is a classic overhead run-and-gun game, supporting up to 4 players in co-op and deathmatch modes.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Commander Genius.sh</path>
		<name>Commander Genius</name>
		<image>./media/Commander Genius.png</image>
		<desc>Commander Genius is a software piece that interprets the Commander Keen Invasion of the Vorticons and Galaxy series.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Devilutionx.sh</path>
		<name>Devilutionx</name>
		<image>./media/Devilutionx.png</image>
		<desc>DevilutionX is a source port of Diablo and Hellfire that strives to make it simple to run the game while providing engine improvements, bugfixes, and some optional quality of life features.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dinothawr.sh</path>
		<name>Dinothawr</name>
		<image>./media/Dinothawr.png</image>
		<desc>A clever and cute push-the-block-in-a-straight-line puzzle game in the spirit of Kickle Cubicle written from the ground up for libretro.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Doom.sh</path>
		<name>Doom</name>
		<image>./media/Doom.png</image>
		<desc>Doom is a 1993 first-person shooter game developed by id Software for MS-DOS.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Doom 2.sh</path>
		<name>Doom 2</name>
		<image>./media/Doom 2.png</image>
		<desc>Doom II is a first-person shooter game by id Software.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Half-Life.sh</path>
		<name>Half-Life</name>
		<image>./media/Half-Life.png</image>
		<desc>Half-Life, a First Person Shooter released by Valve & Sierra in 1998, tells the story of a recently graduated theoretical physicist, named Dr. Gordon Freeman, who is working on experiments in relation to teleportation technology with other scientists in the Black Mesa Research Facility</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Heart of Darkness.sh</path>
		<name>Heart of Darkness</name>
		<image>./media/Heart of Darkness.png</image>
		<desc>HODE is a reimplementation of the engine used by the game 'Heart of Darkness' developed by Amazing Studio.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hydra Castle Labyrinth.sh</path>
		<name>Hydra Castle Labyrinth</name>
		<image>./media/Hydra Castle Labyrinth.png</image>
		<desc>Hydra Castle Labyrinth, originally Meikyuujou Hydra, is a freeware Indie platformer developed by E. Hashimoto.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Maldita Castillas.sh</path>
		<name>Maldita Castilla</name>
		<image>./media/Maldita Castilla.png</image>
		<desc>Maldita Castilla is an action platformer full of actual myths from Spain and some regions of the medieval Europe</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mr. Boom.sh</path>
		<name>Mr. Boom</name>
		<image>./media/Mr. Boom.png</image>
		<desc>A fun, multiplayer and feature-filled clone of the classic Bomberman series, converted from DOS using asm2c. It includes an advanced CPU AI for single-player sessions.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./OpenJazz.sh</path>
		<name>OpenJazz</name>
		<image>./media/OpenJazz.png</image>
		<desc>OpenJazz is a free, open-source version of the classic Jazz Jackrabbit games</desc>
	</game>	
	<game>
		<path>./OpenTyrian.sh</path>
		<name>OpenTyrian</name>
		<image>./media/OpenTyrian.png</image>
		<desc>OpenTyrian is an open-source port of the DOS game Tyrian.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Prehistorik 2.sh</path>
		<name>Prehistorik 2</name>
		<image>./media/Prehistorik 2.png</image>
		<desc>Prehistorik 2 is a platform game, the sequel to Prehistorik. It was developed by Titus Interactive for MS-DOS and Amstrad CPC in 1993.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Quake.sh</path>
		<name>Quake</name>
		<image>./media/Quake.png</image>
		<desc>Quake is a first-person shooter video game developed by id Software and published by GT Interactive in 1996</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Quake 2.sh</path>
		<name>Quake 2</name>
		<image>./media/Quake 2.png</image>
		<desc>Quake II is a first-person shooter video game released in December 1997. It was developed by id Software and published by Activision.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./RAWGL.sh</path>
		<name>RAWGL - Another World</name>
		<image>./media/RAWGL.png</image>
		<desc>RAWGL is a re-implementation of the engine used in the game Another World.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./REminiscence.sh</path>
		<name>REminiscence - Flashback</name>
		<image>./media/REminiscence.png</image>
		<desc>REminiscence is a re-implementation of the engine used in the game Flashback made by Delphine Software and released in 1992.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rick Dangerous.sh</path>
		<name>Rick Dangerous</name>
		<image>./media/Rick Dangerous.png</image>
		<desc>Rick Dangerous is a platform game developed by Core Design.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SDLPoP.sh</path>
		<name>SDL Prince of Persia</name>
		<image>./media/SDLPoP.png</image>
		<desc>SDLPoP is an open-source port of Prince of Persia, based on the disassembly of the DOS version, extended with new features.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shovel Knight.sh</path>
		<name>Shovel Knight</name>
		<image>./media/Shovel Knight.png</image>
		<desc>Shovel Knight is a 2D side-scrolling platform game developed and published by Yacht Club Games.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic 1.sh</path>
		<name>Sonic 1</name>
		<image>./media/Sonic 1.png</image>
		<desc>Sonic the Hedgehog is a platform game developed by Sonic Team and published by Sega for the Sega Genesis home video game console.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic 2.sh</path>
		<name>Sonic 2</name>
		<image>./media/Sonic 2.png</image>
		<desc>Sonic the Hedgehog 2 is a 1992 platform game developed by Sega Technical Institute (STI) for the Sega Genesis.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic CD.sh</path>
		<name>Sonic CD</name>
		<image>./media/Sonic CD.png</image>
		<desc>Sonic the Hedgehog CD is a 1993 platform game for the Sega CD developed and published by Sega.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spelunky.sh</path>
		<name>Spelunky</name>
		<image>./media/Spelunky.png</image>
		<desc>Spelunky is a cave exploration / treasure-hunting game inspired by classic platform games and roguelikes, where the goal is to grab as much treasure from the cave as possible.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./sm64.sh</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64</name>
		<image>./media/sm64.png</image>
		<desc>Super Mario 64 decompilation</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./sorr.sh</path>
		<name>Streets of Rage Remake</name>
		<image>./media/sorr.png</image>
		<desc>Streets of Rage Remake is a remastered version of the MegaDrive classic. You'll go throughout an immense town fighting against people who try to attack you. There are more than 60 different enemies, you can choose among 16 characters, choose your favourite one and kick asses out there.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario War.sh</path>
		<name>Super Mario War</name>
		<image>./media/Super Mario War.png</image>
		<desc>Super Mario War is an open-source, cross-platform, platform-adventure video game and level editor released on 16 December 2006.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SuperTux.sh</path>
		<name>SuperTux</name>
		<image>./media/SuperTux.png</image>
		<desc>SuperTux is a open-source classic 2D jump'n run sidescroller game in a style similar to the original Super Mario games.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Undertale.sh</path>
		<name>Undertale</name>
		<image>./media/Undertale.png</image>
		<desc>Undertale is a 2D role-playing video game created by indie developer Toby Fox</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./VVVVVV.sh</path>
		<name>VVVVVV</name>
		<image>./media/VVVVVV.png</image>
		<desc>VVVVVV is a platform game all about exploring one simple mechanical idea - what if you reversed gravity instead of jumping?</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wolfenstein 3D.sh</path>
		<name>Wolfenstein 3D</name>
		<image>./media/Wolfenstein 3D.png</image>
		<desc>Wolfenstein 3D is a first-person shooter video game developed by id Software and published by Apogee Software and FormGen.</desc>
	</game>
</gameList>
